

ANITA SHAH

UX & UI Designer

https://anitashah92.github.io/ anitashah92@gmail.com 203.912.1689

Based in San Francisco, CA. Open to relocation anywhere in the USA & Canada.

"I'm a creator of beautiful usercentered design solutions. My process involves user research, wireframing, & front-end prototyping. Let's make something amazing!"

SKILLS

Design Expertise

User Survey Hi-Fi Mockups
User Interview Usability Testing

User Personas Branding
User Stories Prototyping
Sketching Typography

Front-End Development

HTML 5 jQuery
CSS 3 Git/Github
Javascript Responsive

Tools

Survey Monkey

Sketch Adobe Photoshop
Figma Adobe Illustrator

Maze

InVision Omnigraffle

Google Forms UserTesting.com

Canva Axure

Jira MailChimp

Microsoft Office Webflow

EDUCATION

2011 - 2015 University of California, San Diego

Bachelors of Science (BS), Psychology & Business

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 -Present Love & Care Marketing Designer

-Currently helping this non-profit create a brand and improve their digital content (including social media, the website, donor-facing newsletters, etc)

-Increased online presence by 30%

-Leading the redesign of the current website

-Conducted initial UX research and conducted interviews

-Work in a collaborative environment with the content team

May 2019 -Nov 2019 Beckett Corp UX/UI Designer

-Helped fulfill Beckett's IoT initiative in which they wanted users to be able to view oil tank metrics via a mobile application

-Used UX methodologies to conduct research and talked to industry specalists

-Translated the data into flows and wireframes

-Conducted user testing to ensure the application would lead to a more intuitive user experience

-Designed hi-fi iOS prototype

-Optimized data visualization techniques

-Worked in an agile environment with a PM and engineers.

Nov 2018-May 2019 Net Zero Enterprises Brand & Design Consultant

-Using an iterative design process, worked collaboratively with the stakeholders of this VC firm to re-brand and design a new website

-Created a moodboard to represent the visual identity of the brand

-Created wireframes and web mockups which were translated to a WordPress site

PROJECTS

2018

Personal Portfolio UX/UI Designer

-Designed and developed my own portfolio site using UI skills and tools including Figma, HTML, CSS, and Javascript.